

## **SOFIA BLOMGREN**

070-692 87 11 sofia.im.blomgren@gmail.com www.sofiablomgren.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm 30 years old and I grew up in Stockholm, Sweden. After high school I moved to Santa Barbara, California, where I studied photography and media for two years at college. Right now I'm finishing up my Master's degree in Media Technology at KTH in Stockholm. I'm also freelancing as a photographer through my own business. I'm a positive person who likes to plan and coordinate things, something that I've practiced a lot through many of the experiences mentioned below. After graduating I want to work with user experiece and, eventually, project management.

#### **EDUCATION**

M.Sc.Eng. Media Technology, M.Sc. Interactive Media Technology	2015-present
KTH Royal Institute of Technology Stockholm, Sweden	
B.Sc. Media Technology	2015-2018
KTH Royal Institute of Technology	

2012-2014

# Certificate of Achievement in Applied Photography

Santa Barbara City College Santa Barbara, CA, USA

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Stockholm, Sweden

Fast Travel Games	Spring 2020
Master Thesis Student	

Researching UX for hand tracking in VR.

#### Ericsson Summer 2019

Summer Intern

Summer intern working with UI and UX design for a VR project.

#### Sofia Blomgren Photography

Owner, Photographer & Videographer

My own business through which I take different freelance photo and video jobs.

2016-present

#### Rockfoto

#### Photo Editor 2016-present

Rockfoto is a photo agency for concert photography. As photo editor, I work as a coordinator between clients, concert promoters and our photographers.

#### Photographer 2015-present

Rockfoto is a photo agency for concert photography. As photographer, I take photos at concerts and then deliver the photos to a tight deadline.

### **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

### Chapter of Media Technology, KTH

Head of the Photo Committee	2018-2019
The Photo Committee is a group for everyone at the chapter	

The Photo Committee is a group for everyone at the chapter who's interested in photography. As head of the committee, I created events for its members and worked together with other committees at the chapter when they needed photographers.

## Project Leader of the Student Reception 2018

I was one of three project leaders of the student reception at the chapter. Being project leader includes recruiting students to work during the reception, planning the whole reception and being main responsible during all reception events.

#### Osqledaren, KTH

Media Producer	2018-2020
Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As media	
producer, I created content for web and social media.	

# **Photo Editor**Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As photo

editor, I was responsible for the photographers and illustrators on the editorial staff and I guided them through the creative process. I was also a part of the paper's project group.

# Photographer2015-2016,Osqledaren is the student union newspaper at KTH. As2017-2018

photographer, I took photos for articles that I was assigned and delivered to a deadline.